<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xml:lang="en"><generator uri="https://jekyllrb.com/" version="3.8.7">Jekyll</generator><link href="https://pdis.nat.gov.tw/en/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/atom+xml" /><link href="https://pdis.nat.gov.tw/en/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" hreflang="en" /><updated>2021-11-04T00:59:00+00:00</updated><id>https://pdis.nat.gov.tw/en/feed.xml</id><author><name>PDIS</name></author><entry><title type="html">Sustainability and development: Great bedfellows</title><link href="https://pdis.nat.gov.tw/en/blog/ESG-%E6%B0%B8%E7%BA%8C%E8%88%87%E5%BD%B1%E9%9F%BF%E5%8A%9B%E6%8A%95%E8%B3%87/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Sustainability and development: Great bedfellows" /><published>2021-10-29T00:00:00+00:00</published><updated>2021-10-29T00:00:00+00:00</updated><id>https://pdis.nat.gov.tw/en/blog/ESG-%E6%B0%B8%E7%BA%8C%E8%88%87%E5%BD%B1%E9%9F%BF%E5%8A%9B%E6%8A%95%E8%B3%87</id><content type="html" xml:base="https://pdis.nat.gov.tw/en/blog/ESG-%E6%B0%B8%E7%BA%8C%E8%88%87%E5%BD%B1%E9%9F%BF%E5%8A%9B%E6%8A%95%E8%B3%87/">&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://pdis.nat.gov.tw/en/blog/%E7%96%AB%E5%BE%8C%E6%8C%AF%E8%88%88-%E4%BA%BA%E4%BA%BA%E6%9C%89%E3%84%97%E3%84%9C%CB%8A/&quot;&gt;In my last column&lt;/a&gt;, I introduced the “Quintuple Stimulus Voucher.” By the end of October, the total number of paper and digital vouchers issued exceeded 19 million. Now that pandemic control measures are gradually easing, shops around Taiwan are filled with customers.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;At the same time as spurring consumption, we are working out how to transform the turbulence brought about by the pandemic into a new impetus to shepherding the economy towards sustainability. One solution shown to work in Taiwan, which combines industrial innovation and sustainable development, is the rapidly developing ESG and impact investment.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;ESG means incorporating “environment,” “social responsibility” and “corporate governance” into an evaluation criteria ensuring business operations have a positive impact on society and individuals. Over the past decade, ESG has become an indispensable part of corporate development. In 2020, the Taiwan Financial Supervisory Commission built upon this foundation in successively promoting the “Corporate Governance 3.0-Sustainable Development Roadmap” and “Green Finance Action Plan 2.0” to accelerate the sustainable development of Taiwan industry from the perspective of corporate governance and financial investment.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The measures adopted by the roadmap include renaming the current corporate social responsibility report to “Sustainability Report or ESG Report,” promoting the publication of all reports in English and strengthening third-party certification from 2023 onwards. In addition to the existing food, chemical, finance and insurance industries, as well as listed companies with capital exceeding NT$5 billion (US$179.9 million), all listed companies with capital exceeding NT$2 billion will need to produce a sustainability report.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The plan, which expands the development of green financial products and services, is an important step taken by Taiwan to promote ESG. In May 2021, the Taiwan OTC Buying Center established a special board for the “Sustainable Development Bond” system. In conjunction, Taiwan’s first batch of socially responsible bonds were issued and listed on the OTC. Social performance and ESG information revealed that all public equity banks will issue green/social responsibility/sustainable development bonds within four years.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Through ESG, more and more Taiwan companies have become the new force of sustainable development. At the same time, the challenges are ever increasing. From coronavirus and climate change to the mental health of the younger generations, the world’s major risks include a variety of environmental and social issues.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This year marks the World Economic Forum’s (WEF) 51st anniversary, and its theme “&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.weforum.org/great-reset/&quot;&gt;The Great Reset&lt;/a&gt;” indicates the gathering of stakeholders and cross-domain cooperation to establish “stakeholder capitalism.” It is heartening that via the efforts of Taiwan’s public sector and participants from all walks of life, the rapid rise of the ESG concept in recent years is one of the acts bringing industry and stakeholders together.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;One example is the “&lt;a href=&quot;https://sert.tw/&quot;&gt;Social Enterprise Revolving Trust&lt;/a&gt;” (SERT) initiated by Taiwan’s private sector. SERT boasts a value of NT$200 million, and is Taiwan’s first charitable trust to invest in social enterprises. It also helps social entrepreneurs obtain seed capital for entrepreneurship. In the past five years, SERT’s total investment and sponsorship has surpassed NT$15 million. In addition, it has made equity investments in five social enterprises (SEs) and has supported numerous social innovators through sponsorships, action projects and scholarship programs.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;During this process, SERT has observed that SEs often have additional communication costs due to gaps in social missions, as well as the perception of company operations whilst facing market pressures. This year, SERT and its strategic partner KPMG have jointly designed the “Social Impact Preferred Stock (SIPS).”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The investment mechanism of SIPS aims to utilize the ability of “special stocks” to negotiate investment conditions. Furthermore, in order to secure the active participation of stakeholders, the company’s articles of association lock in its social objective and add an influence item to the board meeting agenda so as to assure the tracking of the social mission’s achievement. In July, SERT successfully launched its first “Social Impact Special Unit” investment.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;As the saying goes: “If you are not a part of the solution, you are a part of the problem.” Through ESG and impact investment, Taiwan is getting to the heart of the matter in charting a new post-pandemic course through which sustainability and development play an equally important role.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>Audrey Tang, Sheau-Tyng Peng</name></author><category term="blog" /><category term="Social Innovation" /><summary type="html">Through ESG and impact investment, Taiwan is getting to the heart of the matter in charting a new post-pandemic course.</summary><media:thumbnail xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" url="https://pdis.nat.gov.tw/en/assets/imgs/money-2696219_1280.jpg" /><media:content medium="image" url="https://pdis.nat.gov.tw/en/assets/imgs/money-2696219_1280.jpg" xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" /></entry><entry><title type="html">Remarks at the EU DisinfoLab Annual Conference</title><link href="https://pdis.nat.gov.tw/en/blog/EU-DisinfoLab-%E5%B9%B4%E5%BA%A6%E7%A0%94%E8%A8%8E%E6%9C%83%E8%87%B4%E8%A9%9E/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Remarks at the EU DisinfoLab Annual Conference" /><published>2021-10-29T00:00:00+00:00</published><updated>2021-10-29T00:00:00+00:00</updated><id>https://pdis.nat.gov.tw/en/blog/EU-DisinfoLab-%E5%B9%B4%E5%BA%A6%E7%A0%94%E8%A8%8E%E6%9C%83%E8%87%B4%E8%A9%9E</id><content type="html" xml:base="https://pdis.nat.gov.tw/en/blog/EU-DisinfoLab-%E5%B9%B4%E5%BA%A6%E7%A0%94%E8%A8%8E%E6%9C%83%E8%87%B4%E8%A9%9E/">&lt;p&gt;In this age of social media and flourishing online technologies, disinformation can spread like a virus. It goes viral. In pluralistic democracies, such as Taiwan, disinformation poses a complex challenge—because anyone armed with a smartphone and basic editing tools can take part in its dissemination.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Prior to the pandemic - prior to 2020 - Taiwan had already been cited as the country most exposed to disinformation operations. The attacks largely come from the PRC regime in Beijing, and we know their motivations: to destabilize our democracy, society, and government institutions in order to impose their brand of authoritarianism.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;For example, during the anti-ELAB protests in Hong Kong, a trending message made its rounds across Taiwan’s social-media landscape, attempting to portray the Hong Kong protesters as so-called “rioters” who allegedly were paid $20 million to murder members of the police force. That, of course, was a gross misrepresentation of the protestors’ mission, but the intention of the campaign was clear: to lessen the influence of the anti-ELAB movement on the Taiwanese presidential election. The message was actually trending only on Taiwanese social media, because the citizens of Hong Kong would have easily seen through the veil of disinformation. The message was not meant for a Hong Kong audience.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;According to Taiwan FactCheck Center, this piece of disinformation was traced back to the Weibo account of 中央政法委长安剑, the PRC Central Political and Law Unit. They had created the original fabrication by misusing a Reuters photo, attempting to paint the image as a depiction of teenage protestors engaging in violent activity simply over the purchase of iPhones. The second-level remixers then built on the image by creating supporting narratives. This disinformation campaign was clearly attributed to the PRC regime.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Taiwan faces disinformation campaigns such as these on a daily – indeed, hourly - basis. This trend has been further exacerbated by the coronavirus pandemic, with an estimated 25% of all pandemic-related disinformation believed to have come from the PRC.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;As the COVID-19 pandemic swept across the globe, pandemic anxiety has stoked the flames of disinformation—and we’ve seen the challenges posed by pandemic-related misinformation, mal-information, disinformation, ultimately leading to our so-called “infodemic,” as the WHO calls it.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Instead of using centralized initiatives in order to fight the ongoing ‘infodemic,’ Taiwan employs a decentralized, human-centered approach. During the pandemic, Taiwan adopted what I call the “fast, fair, and fun” approach, and the “humor over rumor” tactic to combat coronavirus misinformation, which gives the public room to laugh at nonfactual information.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Here’s a fun example. In Taiwan, we have a cute Shiba Inu, or 總柴, who translates all of the information published by the Central Epidemic Command Center, or CECC, using very cute dog pictures. For example, for physical distancing, we have a picture that says, “If you’re outdoors, please keep the space of two Shiba Inus away, and if you’re indoors, keep the space of three dogs away from one another.”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Another instance from February last year shows how we used viral humor not only to disseminate science, but to combat disinformation—‘fighting fire with fire,’ as it were.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;At that time, we saw the online spread of false allegations claiming that Taiwan’s increased medical grade face-mask production had compromised its ability to make bathroom tissue paper. To keep people from hoarding toilet paper, we released a meme featuring Taiwan’s Premier Su Tseng-chang—who is the head of the Cabinet—shaking his backside, along with the caption, “We only have one pair of buttocks.” Let me explain the humor: The word “stockpile” is pronounced in Mandarin as “囤,” which sounds exactly like buttocks, or “臀.” The picture also showed a table clarifying that materials for toilet paper are imported from South America and have no bearing on medical mask production, because raw materials for masks are sourced locally.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The logic behind our strategies is very simple. Any approach that begins with censorship faces extensive resistance—because in a pluralistic democracy, any communication that looks like a takedown or censorship is simply a nonstarter. Therefore, we need to think of innovative ways to outrun and outpace the conspiracy theorists and disinformation campaigns.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This is not easy, because most disinformation is motivated by outrage, which is one of the most viral emotions. Outrage leads to revenge, discrimination, and the beginnings of hate speech, rendering people’s capacity for empathy null and void. When people start sharing stories with mindless abandon, we then have the real problem of an “infodemic” on our hands. Because of this, we need to vaccinate ourselves against the “virus of the mind.” We now realize that humor has a very high “R-value” and has the capacity to spread more dramatically than even outrage, as proven quite effectively in Taiwan. So far, we’ve succeeded in containing the “infodemic” without censorship or top-down “takedowns.”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Personally, I believe it’s difficult for a single piece of disinformation to get everybody enraged if people are competent in critical and creative thinking. It’s just like biodiversity—it’s harder for a biological virus to take hold if there is ample biodiversity in the ecosystem. The same idea holds for democracy.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In Taiwan, we put an emphasis on “media competence” (媒體素養) instead of “media literacy” (媒體識讀). This is a conscious choice, because in Mandarin, literacy, or 識讀, assumes that you’re a reader or a viewer, a consumer of information, whereas competence, or 素養, means that you’re a producer, a co-creator—a steward of information, data, and media.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The government of Taiwan has incorporated media competence into our basic training modules, not just for basic education, but also for government and educational personnel in a variety of ways. For example, the Ministry of Education established the Media Competence Education Promotion Committee, which convenes once every four months to review and formulate policy.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We are putting efforts in building related core competencies among students in accordance with our 12-year Basic Education General Guidelines, and media competence has also been included in various seminars and training workshops for educational and government personnel.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Instead of a standard answer-based media education system, we are looking to incorporate lifelong lessons in media production and newsroom operations, such that people can see themselves as contributors to journalism. Compared to censorship and takedowns, I believe this is a longer-lasting solution, or “vaccine,” to the ongoing disinformation crisis.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Taiwan’s resolve to combat online disinformation stems from its grounding as one of Asia’s most open societies. In addition, I would also say that Taiwan takes freedom of speech extremely seriously, regarding it as a right that cannot be traded in any shape or form.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Even in the face of a global pandemic, Taiwan ranked 5th in the world and 1st in Asia in the most recent “Freedom on the Net 2021” report published by Freedom House in September. I believe the reason behind this achievement is our vibrant online landscape, supported by meaningful and affordable internet access, an independent judiciary that protects free expression, and the administration that has worked to make its system and policy rationale as transparent as possible to our citizens.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;When it comes to debunking disinformation, again, we do not believe that a centralized and opaque approach is the most reliable. To prevent its further dissemination, disinformation is verified and clarified through joint endeavors by what I call a People-Public-Private Partnership. We have established a government mechanism that offers immediate and effective clarification and a neutral, independent, third-party fact-checking and media self-regulation mechanism.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;For example, platforms such as the g0v community invites citizens to engage in open collaboration and work together to identify disinformation, developing apps such as the Cofacts LINE bot. Other mechanisms involve consultations by experts, such as the Taiwan FactCheck Center, which was accredited in November 2018 as a third-party fact checker by the International Fact-Checking Network.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In a sense, disinformation is just a symptom of a larger disease. Disinformation is the result of a lack of trust among the people, but also between the governments and their citizens.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In Taiwan, we deeply embrace democracy, humanity, openness and freedom of speech. With these core values, we can create a friendly environment for collective intelligence and social innovation. With intense efforts from the social, public and private sectors, now we know there is a way to augment transparency and give scientific knowledge a higher basic transmission rate than conspiracy theories and innuendo.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;With that, I would like to extend my sincerest appreciation for the kind invitation to the EU DisinfoLab. I trust the discussions will be lively and interesting, leading to concrete and meaningful actionable results.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>Audrey Tang, Frances Feng</name></author><category term="blog" /><category term="Open Government" /><category term="Social Innovation" /><summary type="html">It’s difficult for a single piece of disinformation to get everybody enraged if people are competent in critical and creative thinking.</summary><media:thumbnail xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" url="https://pdis.nat.gov.tw/en/assets/imgs/light-553527_1280.jpg" /><media:content medium="image" url="https://pdis.nat.gov.tw/en/assets/imgs/light-553527_1280.jpg" xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" /></entry><entry><title type="html">From triple coupon to five times coupon</title><link href="https://pdis.nat.gov.tw/en/blog/%E5%BE%9E%E4%B8%89%E5%80%8D%E5%88%B8%E5%88%B0%E4%BA%94%E5%80%8D%E5%88%B8/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="From triple coupon to five times coupon" /><published>2021-10-14T00:00:00+00:00</published><updated>2021-10-14T00:00:00+00:00</updated><id>https://pdis.nat.gov.tw/en/blog/%E5%BE%9E%E4%B8%89%E5%80%8D%E5%88%B8%E5%88%B0%E4%BA%94%E5%80%8D%E5%88%B8</id><content type="html" xml:base="https://pdis.nat.gov.tw/en/blog/%E5%BE%9E%E4%B8%89%E5%80%8D%E5%88%B8%E5%88%B0%E4%BA%94%E5%80%8D%E5%88%B8/">&lt;p&gt;Since the outbreak of the epidemic this year, Taiwan has once again defended the invasion of the virus with the concerted efforts of all the people. In order to encourage the people to use consumption to support local businesses to regain their strength, the administrative team borrowed from the experience of revitalizing the triple coupon last year and planned a five-fold coupon this year. From three times to five times, what matters is not only the quota, but also the multiplier effect created by the government and the people.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Recently, I attended training courses in various agencies. Many civil servants want to talk about the imagination of a “smart country”: Some people think that the country must be smart and the administrative process must be completely paperless; but for me, the country must To be wise, we must first have “smart citizens”, that is, starting from the needs of the whole people, combining the creativity of the people, and providing diversified services as much as possible.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The same is true for the five times coupon plan. Rather than developing a new system that requires everyone to re-establish their habits, we choose the “real-name mask system” process that everyone is already familiar with, and we can easily book through the community’s super business machine or mobile phone. Some people want to help the family members who are less familiar with the number to bind together. Such a real need can also be achieved here, and it can be achieved with the smallest possible gap.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Last year’s user feedback is also a reference for improving the design. For example, the last time restrictions on consumption were made by brick-and-mortar businesses, but e-commerce and delivery platforms have become part of everyone’s lives during the epidemic prevention period. This year, these platforms actively respond to the policy and are willing to assist local businesses, small farmers, sheltered workshops and other stores to put them on the shelves, so they can also be included in the scope of use of revitalization coupons, so that more and more people who consume online can be rewarded without changing their lifestyles. Benefit local businesses and create more wins together.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Another pain point is that for those who use digital binding, even if the merchant offers extra coded consumer discounts, it was not easy to find that they could not get the same courtesy as using paper. This time we have added a “digital label”, and after binding, we will get a discount code for the store to verify and give discounts. For traditional merchants such as vendors and self-government associations that have not yet joined the digital payment system, the Ministry of Economic Affairs has also proposed diversified payment incentive programs such as the “Taiwan Cloud Market” to assist in digital transformation.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In addition to the five times coupons, the registration of additional coupons for major ministries also took into account the pain points of the people who took time to register on different platforms last year, and changed to a one-stop check of the coupons you want. You can also find integrated information if you want to know the binding status, usage quota, and lottery results.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;On the first day the five times coupons were used, 4 million digital coupons were already bound, more than twice as many as last year, and 12 million paper bookings were successfully booked. Provide multiple choices and fully reflect needs. Although some friends find it complicated, this is like the application of “AI”. If multiple needs are limited to a single channel, it will easily fall into the arrogance of authoritarian “Authoritarian Intelligence”; only assistance The “Assistive Intelligence” of the people can give full play to the power of the wisdom of the people.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>Audrey Tang, Joke</name></author><category term="blog" /><category term="Social Innovation" /><summary type="html">The Ministry of Economic Affairs has also proposed multiple payment incentive programs such as the &quot;Taiwan Cloud Market&quot; to assist in digital transformation.</summary><media:thumbnail xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" url="https://pdis.nat.gov.tw/en/assets/imgs/apples-1841132_1920.jpg" /><media:content medium="image" url="https://pdis.nat.gov.tw/en/assets/imgs/apples-1841132_1920.jpg" xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" /></entry><entry><title type="html">Youth Medical Examination Government Website-the starting point of the partnership</title><link href="https://pdis.nat.gov.tw/en/blog/%E9%9D%92%E5%B9%B4%E9%AB%94%E6%AA%A2%E6%94%BF%E5%BA%9C%E7%B6%B2%E7%AB%99-%E5%A4%A5%E4%BC%B4%E9%97%9C%E4%BF%82%E7%9A%84%E8%B5%B7%E9%BB%9E/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Youth Medical Examination Government Website-the starting point of the partnership" /><published>2021-10-05T00:00:00+00:00</published><updated>2021-10-05T00:00:00+00:00</updated><id>https://pdis.nat.gov.tw/en/blog/%E9%9D%92%E5%B9%B4%E9%AB%94%E6%AA%A2%E6%94%BF%E5%BA%9C%E7%B6%B2%E7%AB%99-%E5%A4%A5%E4%BC%B4%E9%97%9C%E4%BF%82%E7%9A%84%E8%B5%B7%E9%BB%9E</id><content type="html" xml:base="https://pdis.nat.gov.tw/en/blog/%E9%9D%92%E5%B9%B4%E9%AB%94%E6%AA%A2%E6%94%BF%E5%BA%9C%E7%B6%B2%E7%AB%99-%E5%A4%A5%E4%BC%B4%E9%97%9C%E4%BF%82%E7%9A%84%E8%B5%B7%E9%BB%9E/">&lt;p&gt;“Ziyi, Youqian, Zhiyao, Yijun, good morning!” Zhuang Zhewei from the Forest Service Bureau enthusiastically greeted the students in the group. Calling out the names of the students eagerly, without hesitation.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This is the result of the 2021 “Rescue Action by Youth, RAY 5.0” (Rescue Action by Youth, RAY 5.0). The students were eager to show off their hard work over the past two months. Some groups took a break at four o’clock in the morning, and then changed their outfits to prepare to participate in the results presentation. The team carefully prepared the final results for the announcement, and also carefully thought out the theme of the clothing: “Mountain and forest style, because we are redesigning “Mountain Forest Leisure Net” for the Forest Service Bureau.”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This year RAY 5.0, from Among the 130 applicants, 14 outstanding young students were selected and rolled up their sleeves to transform government digital services. They come from diverse backgrounds such as design, research, and information. They have contributed to their summer vacation, starting with in-depth interviews, and reinventing the “difficult to use” government digital services for many people.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The students responsible for redesigning the Taipei City Public Care Registration System interviewed many novice parents to understand their needs and difficulties. According to their needs, the registration process of public trusteeship was redesigned. During the interview, a mother held her child in one hand and was busy operating the public care system with the other. The students carefully noticed this detail and made up their minds: to make a mobile phone version that can be easily operated with one hand.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Zhuang Zhewei of the Forest Service Bureau also shared in the press conference: “The manufacturer jokingly said, why do we even have a meeting with our classmates on the evening of Chinese Valentine’s Day? But seeing our classmates give so enthusiastically, of course we Full support too!”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In the past, agencies often used their own imaginations to demand design services. “During the interview, the students used skills to guide users to express their real difficulties and needs. And through this opportunity, we also understand that users are really different from what we think. We are usually too familiar with it. This service, on the contrary, did not see the blind spots of the service.” A colleague from the Taoyuan City Social Bureau who is also one of the transformation services shared her experience.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In the results presentation, we also specially invited the chiefs of various agencies to try out the simulation service designed by the students. The deputy director of the Forest Service actually operated the chat robot redesigned by the students through the ingeniously arranged situation of the students. “For us, this is really a good way to optimize the experience of the elderly!” The Forest Service also launched the bidding process for new services immediately after the meeting, hoping that this new experience can be provided to the general public in the near future People use.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Participation in the user interviews and tests led by youths by colleagues from the government agencies not only allows students to understand the challenges and difficulties encountered by the government in providing services. It also allows the organization to feel the full professionalism and enthusiasm of the classmates, and each time the participation of young people becomes the starting point of trust and partnership. Optimizing the big and small affairs around you and me requires everyone’s strength. Let us roll up our sleeves and make public services better!&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>唐鳳、張皓婷</name></author><category term="blog" /><category term="開放政府" /><category term="青年參與" /><summary type="html">Seeing the dedication of the students so enthusiastically, of course we also have to give our full support.</summary><media:thumbnail xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" url="https://pdis.nat.gov.tw/en/assets/imgs/AmVZEjF7e6hndaBEbKhI.jpeg" /><media:content medium="image" url="https://pdis.nat.gov.tw/en/assets/imgs/AmVZEjF7e6hndaBEbKhI.jpeg" xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" /></entry><entry><title type="html">A chosen future: Stimulating the post-pandemic bounceback</title><link href="https://pdis.nat.gov.tw/en/blog/%E7%96%AB%E5%BE%8C%E6%8C%AF%E8%88%88-%E4%BA%BA%E4%BA%BA%E6%9C%89%E3%84%97%E3%84%9C%CB%8A/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="A chosen future: Stimulating the post-pandemic bounceback" /><published>2021-09-27T00:00:00+00:00</published><updated>2021-09-27T00:00:00+00:00</updated><id>https://pdis.nat.gov.tw/en/blog/%E7%96%AB%E5%BE%8C%E6%8C%AF%E8%88%88-%E4%BA%BA%E4%BA%BA%E6%9C%89%E3%84%97%E3%84%9C%CB%8A</id><content type="html" xml:base="https://pdis.nat.gov.tw/en/blog/%E7%96%AB%E5%BE%8C%E6%8C%AF%E8%88%88-%E4%BA%BA%E4%BA%BA%E6%9C%89%E3%84%97%E3%84%9C%CB%8A/">&lt;p&gt;Since Taiwan raised its national pandemic alert in May, consumption patterns have undergone tremendous change. As physical channels and on-site activities are constrained, finding ways to create new opportunities for products and services are the top priority in all sectors of the economy.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Through the groundbreaking approach of public-private collaboration, challenges were transformed into opportunities. Last year, the Small and Medium Enterprise Administration under the Ministry of Economic Affairs, which has long been mentoring and training Taiwan’s social innovation organizations, established the “A Chosen Future” project. Involving 75 annually awarded social innovation and quality manufacturers, the initiative is based on the key theme of U.N. Sustainable Development Goal 12: responsible consumption and production.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The project’s Mandarin name features the phonetic “zé”, which represents a combination of “responsible”（責） production and “selective”（擇） consumption. It further opens consumer’s minds to the meaning of “zé,” laying the foundations for forging a “future with choices” together.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Faced with the impact of COVID-19, the SMEA continued cultivating opportunities for social innovation organizations, as well as fast-tracking negotiations on intellectual property co-branding, pop-up stores and various e-commerce channels. One highlight was the launch in July of the “A Chosen Future Online Flagship Store” by the SMEA and homegrown e-commerce heavyweight PChome. The first wave of 20 social innovation brands, including natural ingredients and environmentally friendly products, won widespread praise upon debut.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Inspired by the “A Chosen Future Online Flagship Store”, the government launched the “Quintuple Stimulus Voucher” in September, employing the same approach to encourage customers to return to bricks-and-mortar stores. The undertaking is part of the government’s Relief Package 4.0 program, which has assisted over 11 million people since June. Vouchers valued at NT$5,000 (US$181) will be issued. Any nationals born before April 30, 2022, as well as foreigners who obtain permanent residency before this date, can spend the voucher in a store using a paper voucher or reimbursement via credit card and mobile payment systems.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Taiwan e-commerce platforms are part and parcel of the initiative for the first time. Each platform will set up a dedicated area for the promotion of the vouchers, so that consumption focuses on local businesses and small farmers. Modeled after the “A Chosen Future” project, the strategy dovetails with new consumption patterns and ensures the government’s coronavirus-support net is cast wider.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Drawing on the lessons of last year’s successful stimulus voucher experience, many adjustments have been made to increase convenience. For example, up to four separate stimulus voucher allocations can be linked to an individual account through the OTP of the National Health Insurance Express App.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Furthermore, the “Quintuple Stimulus Voucher” incorporates a QR Code setting. A discount QR code will be issued upon digital linking. Whether it is for a physical purchase or online consumption, as long as the QR Code is entered at the time of order or checkout, it can link to a voucher. In addition to enjoying the corresponding savings, consumers can confirm the vouchers are used for desired businesses or products.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The objective of SDG 12 is to ensure sustainable consumption and production. From service design to consumption process, through public-private collaboration on social innovation, the “Quintuple Stimulus Voucher” is another shining example of Taiwan finding flexible approaches for spurring the post-pandemic economic bounceback whilst creating a new model for the development of sustainable business.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>Audrey Tang, Sheau-Tyng Peng</name></author><category term="blog" /><category term="Social Innovation" /><summary type="html">“Quintuple Stimulus Voucher” is another shining example of Taiwan finding flexible approaches for spurring the post-pandemic economic bounceback.</summary><media:thumbnail xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" url="https://pdis.nat.gov.tw/en/assets/imgs/article-615133ce59d06.jpg" /><media:content medium="image" url="https://pdis.nat.gov.tw/en/assets/imgs/article-615133ce59d06.jpg" xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" /></entry><entry><title type="html">Cool system, heartwarming service</title><link href="https://pdis.nat.gov.tw/en/blog/%E5%86%B7%E7%B3%BB%E7%B5%B1-%E6%9A%96%E6%9C%8D%E5%8B%99/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Cool system, heartwarming service" /><published>2021-09-16T00:00:00+00:00</published><updated>2021-09-16T00:00:00+00:00</updated><id>https://pdis.nat.gov.tw/en/blog/%E5%86%B7%E7%B3%BB%E7%B5%B1-%E6%9A%96%E6%9C%8D%E5%8B%99</id><content type="html" xml:base="https://pdis.nat.gov.tw/en/blog/%E5%86%B7%E7%B3%BB%E7%B5%B1-%E6%9A%96%E6%9C%8D%E5%8B%99/">&lt;p&gt;With the international rush and the geopolitical situation, every vaccine in Taiwan is hard to come by. Unlike previous years’ vaccinations, this time we not only had to consider the public’s acceptance of each brand, willingness to administer, timing, and location, but also had to evaluate the best overall vaccination layout with the timing, quantity, and brand of vaccines arriving.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The “1922 Vaccine Registration and Appointment Platform”, which was launched in July, was created with such complex considerations in mind. Unlike the flu vaccine, which can be administered in the order of the household registration, the platform must consider the vaccine type, quantity, and brand, as well as the public’s acceptance of the vaccine brand, their willingness to receive the vaccine, the time and place of administration, in order to accurately and effectively dispense the vaccine.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The platform is designed to seamlessly connect the demand side and the supply side so that each precious vaccine can be administered in the shortest possible time. Therefore, in the planning of the system, we focus on a few core principles:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;First, we must strive to meet the needs of local governments in terms of implementation. In order to avoid conflicting needs among local governments, we should have many conversations and reach a consensus with local governments beforehand.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Second, the public should be able to fully express their wishes on the vaccine brand, time and location, and more importantly, maintain the room for adjustment at any time with the arrival of different brands.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Finally, for people who work, live and are domiciled in different places, it is important to avoid the risk of contracting the vaccine by traveling from one place to another.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It was a challenge to reconcile these principles. Fortunately, the local government was able to do its best to notify the public and successfully complete its mission, using telephone appointments, walk-in registrations, and village and neighborhood leaders to assist people in making appointments.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;As the arrival of vaccines became more stable, the Central Epidemic Command Center began to expand the target population for vaccination, opening up the vaccination to foreigners who are legally resident but do not have a health insurance card, and also planning to gradually open up the vaccination to adolescents under the age of 18 and those who have a household registration but no health insurance status.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Under this policy, the data flow of the system is integrated into the inter-agency data of the Ministry of Foreign Affairs, the Immigration Department, and the Ministry of the Interior, and for the first time is consolidated into a single window with a single ID number, passport number, and entry/exit permit number. Daily statistics are also made available as &lt;a href=&quot;https://data.cdc.gov.tw/dataset/covid-19-vaccine-booking-waiting-counts&quot;&gt;open data&lt;/a&gt; for immediate reference.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We are pleased that local health bureaus and civil affairs bureaus have responded that the system has shown significant improvement over door-to-door notification system the past. Not only can we avoid inadvertent mix-ups, but we can also accurately deploy manpower and materials at the vaccination stations, so that the original 40-50% vaccination rate at the vaccination stations can be greatly increased to over 90%.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It cannot be denied that in practice, the central government continues to receive feedback from front-line colleagues in local governments about the need to make repeated appointments for people who have already received their first dose before the system goes online, and the time and effort required to compile the registry, etc. Many people have also commented that it is not easy to understand their wishes to register and make vaccine appointments, and have suggested ideas for improvement. For each specific suggestion, we carefully evaluate and adjust to make the vaccination process smoother.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We also receive heartwarming responses from the feedbacks, for example from young people who took the initiative to help their parents register and make appointments online, creating a family bond and becoming a topic of conversation between parents and children. Although the epidemic has forced us to restrict our environment, it has also allowed us to see and cherish our friends and family again. We hope that with the concerted efforts of all sectors, the epidemic will be brought under control soon, so that we can resume social activities and enjoy the happiness of human relationships by chatting and dining together.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>Audrey Tang, Mickey Peng</name></author><category term="blog" /><summary type="html">For each specific suggestion, we carefully evaluate and adjust to make the vaccination process smoother.</summary><media:thumbnail xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" url="https://pdis.nat.gov.tw/en/assets/imgs/coffee-1974841_1280.jpg" /><media:content medium="image" url="https://pdis.nat.gov.tw/en/assets/imgs/coffee-1974841_1280.jpg" xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" /></entry><entry><title type="html">Time management is also a kind of independent learning</title><link href="https://pdis.nat.gov.tw/en/blog/%E9%A2%A8%E5%82%B3%E5%AA%92-%E6%99%82%E9%96%93%E7%AE%A1%E7%90%86%E4%B9%9F%E6%98%AF%E4%B8%80%E7%A8%AE%E8%87%AA%E4%B8%BB%E5%AD%B8%E7%BF%92/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Time management is also a kind of independent learning" /><published>2021-09-07T00:00:00+00:00</published><updated>2021-09-07T00:00:00+00:00</updated><id>https://pdis.nat.gov.tw/en/blog/%E9%A2%A8%E5%82%B3%E5%AA%92:%E6%99%82%E9%96%93%E7%AE%A1%E7%90%86%E4%B9%9F%E6%98%AF%E4%B8%80%E7%A8%AE%E8%87%AA%E4%B8%BB%E5%AD%B8%E7%BF%92</id><content type="html" xml:base="https://pdis.nat.gov.tw/en/blog/%E9%A2%A8%E5%82%B3%E5%AA%92-%E6%99%82%E9%96%93%E7%AE%A1%E7%90%86%E4%B9%9F%E6%98%AF%E4%B8%80%E7%A8%AE%E8%87%AA%E4%B8%BB%E5%AD%B8%E7%BF%92/">&lt;p&gt;In August, high school students in Taiwan spent the longest summer vacation due to the epidemic. At the same time, the public hearing of “Class Time for National and High Schools”, which has attracted the attention of all walks of life, has completed the preliminary collection of opinions in the online participation of more than a hundred students.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This public hearing and the 87th Open Government Collaboration Meeting of the Ministry of Education in charge of senior secondary school students’ work and rest time planning and implementation of precautions was derived from a middle school student’s public policy network in December last year Participate in the proposal of the platform (hereinafter referred to as the JOIN platform), “The school time for national high schools will be changed from 09:30 to 05:00”, and I hope to postpone the school time. In fact, as early as 2016, high school students put forward a proposal on the JOIN platform that “the current high school students in Taiwan generally lack sleep, and the time for high school students to go to school should be delayed.” At that time, after the Ministry of Education received opinions from all walks of life, it established norms for the definition of the number of learning sessions and non-learning sessions, and the aforementioned “Notes” were born. Five years later, the students clamored again, just in time for the system to have a chance to be discussed and reviewed.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;“Let students learn to manage their own time, isn’t it a manifestation of letting students “learn independently”?” Some parents supported the proposal at the meeting. However, some NGOs released the results of online questionnaire surveys, and only 18% of parents agreed. 
The objections include the inconvenience of parents to pick up and drop off, the trend of tutoring students to go home later, the content of the syllabus cannot be taught, the students will only go to bed later when the class is postponed, and the students cannot manage their time… etc., some media outlets The results of the road survey are no different from our pre-conference review of opinions.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;When we assisted the National Education Administration to start the preparations for the collaborative meeting, the first task was to sort out people with different positions and what reasons they would support and oppose. Only in this way can we learn more about who can be invited to participate in order to ensure the diversity of opinions. 
However, the collaborative meeting must go one step further and ask the “core questions”. Even if everyone has their own standards and views, is there a basic consensus that people with different positions agree with, or at least an undeniable bottom line? For example, no one is opposed to “making students more efficient in learning”, which can be the core issue.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Based on this, the National Education Department asked the National Health Institute for help to explain the causes and effects of adolescents’ sleep based on empirical data. The briefing of the National Health Institute presents two main points:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ol&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;The recommended amount of sleep for adolescents and adults is indeed different. The recommended amount for adolescents from 14 to 17 years old is 8-10 hours, and for 18 to 64 years old, it is reduced to 7-9 hours.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;It is normal for adolescents to be awake at night and sleepy during the day due to the physiological factors of “delayed sleep cycle”.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This means that when discussing issues, if we say that students are lazy if they can’t wake up in the morning, and that they love to go to bed late, it is not fair.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;figure&gt;
  &lt;img src=&quot;/assets/imgs/5f33aa5426fc726f7ed98217ff4d08f3b3ea0b93.jpeg&quot; /&gt;
  &lt;figcaption&gt;Adolescent sleep delay diagram (taken from the briefing of the National Health Service)&lt;/figcaption&gt;
&lt;/figure&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In addition, the competent authority of the middle school is the local government, and the National Education Administration is based on its power and responsibility. Being able to respond to the high school part is also a prerequisite for participants to understand. When the dialogue can be based on empirical data, everyone is willing to work together to find solutions to improve student learning efficiency, and the discussion can follow in-depth and constructive.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Originally scheduled to hold a public hearing in the south and north, but it was changed to be handled online in response to the epidemic prevention policy. The gain from the epidemic is that everyone’s information capabilities have been significantly improved. Relying on the painstaking details of the National Education Administration and the high level of participation from all walks of life, the online public hearing of the National Education Administration has not only expanded the number of participants, but also has a very smooth meeting process. In the two public hearings, 60% of online participants were students, as well as representatives of local governments, parents, teachers, and related organizations in the jurisdiction of the country. There were about 165 and 360 people watching the live broadcast.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I am very happy that long-distance living has not diminished everyone’s enthusiasm for public affairs. I also saw the students make full preparations, and they were all sound and reasonable within the 3 minutes of speaking time. Some students said that the time of arrival at school is not the key point. First, they advocated the abolition of the North Korean Association, because the school can send any information through class guides, websites, or social software, and it is not a physical collection to be effective. It is also said that the appeal for arriving late is not to be lazy, but to live in a remote home, travel time is very long, and long-term lack of sleep and study will be greatly reduced. The opposing opinion is that as long as it is self-disciplined, the school stipulates that it can cooperate in several classes.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Colorful exchanges of opinions, from the implementation of flexible use of non-learning periods, spot checks for irregularities, to the review of the twelve-year syllabus, and the return to democratic procedures in each school. Students should be asked to work together to meet the needs of the school. Work and rest. The online software’s message board was also active in the conference. The students even set up an “offline discussion forum” on the message board because they did not agree with each other’s opinions, inviting each other to continue discussions on LINE and Facebook.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;figure&gt;
  &lt;img src=&quot;/assets/imgs/c0194a319af8af0b34f25ba0c700e61bf2a8b906.jpeg&quot; /&gt;
  &lt;figcaption&gt;The online meeting room of the public hearing on August 19th class time&lt;/figcaption&gt;
&lt;/figure&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Preliminary preparations, live broadcast and subsequent verbatim records of the public hearing, provided The National Education Administration was able to improve the nutrients for attention; all the participants worked together to add fuelwood to the open government. At the moment when some countries restrict students’ right to choose by controlling online game companies, we are discussing how to allow students to have more room for self-management. Like the teachers and parents who spoke on the same day, I would like to express the deepest affirmation for the students’ high degree of enthusiasm for investing in public issues.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>Audrey Tang, Yi-Wen Chan</name></author><category term="blog" /><category term="Open Government" /><category term="Policy Communication" /><category term="Youth Empowerment" /><summary type="html">During the epidemic, hundreds of students used video conferencing to continue to care about public issues.</summary><media:thumbnail xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" url="https://pdis.nat.gov.tw/en/assets/imgs/5df69fad3ded3d72a09f71b8edf2d97a9a22f5f2.jpeg" /><media:content medium="image" url="https://pdis.nat.gov.tw/en/assets/imgs/5df69fad3ded3d72a09f71b8edf2d97a9a22f5f2.jpeg" xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" /></entry><entry><title type="html">The Gold Standard: 1922 SMS</title><link href="https://pdis.nat.gov.tw/en/blog/%E7%9C%81%E5%8A%9B%E5%AE%89%E5%BF%83%E7%9A%84%E7%B0%A1%E8%A8%8A%E5%AF%A6%E8%81%AF%E5%88%B6/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="The Gold Standard: 1922 SMS" /><published>2021-08-26T00:00:00+00:00</published><updated>2021-08-26T00:00:00+00:00</updated><id>https://pdis.nat.gov.tw/en/blog/%E7%9C%81%E5%8A%9B%E5%AE%89%E5%BF%83%E7%9A%84%E7%B0%A1%E8%A8%8A%E5%AF%A6%E8%81%AF%E5%88%B6</id><content type="html" xml:base="https://pdis.nat.gov.tw/en/blog/%E7%9C%81%E5%8A%9B%E5%AE%89%E5%BF%83%E7%9A%84%E7%B0%A1%E8%A8%8A%E5%AF%A6%E8%81%AF%E5%88%B6/">&lt;p&gt;After the 1922 SMS contact tracing system was released in May, it quickly became part of daily life in Taiwan. Using a smartphone’s built-in camera without an additional app, the simple and easy sytem is now an intuitive habit for most people visiting public spaces.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Data collected via 1922 SMS is stored by the telecommunications provider corresponding to each individual smartphone number. This begs the question: How is this data used appropriately for the purposes of contact tracing whilst also guaranteeing information security? For this reason, Taiwan’s Central Epidemic Command Center has created a “Contact Tracing Assistance Platform” that can be used by front-line contact tracing staff to rapidly grasp the projected scope of impact for any outbreak. This platform contains a number of tools, including an integrated heat map, a contact tracing trajectory, and 1922 SMS records for contact tracing inquiries.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Contact tracing staff routinely need to conduct inquiries relating to the digital footprint of specific cell phone numbers in order to assess the projected scope of an outbreak. The &lt;a href=&quot;https://sms.1922.gov.tw&quot;&gt;1922 SMS - Access record inquiries service&lt;/a&gt; is an example of how the public can check whether their data is being used appropriately. They simply need to visit the website, authenticate with their smartphone number to review the associated registration records and see if the data has been accessed by contact tracing staff within the previous 28 days.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;A point to note is that when contact tracing staff submit an application to inquire about a specific number, the application for data records is submitted to the associated telecommunications service provider via the “Contact Tracing Assistance Platform.” Once the check-in records are obtained, they can only be accessed online and never saved. The platform’s database can only make a record of which contact tracing unit, at what time, checked the cell phone number. After 28 days, the records are deleted in its entirety.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The key here is embodying the principle of open government: Accountability.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Furthermore, when new challenges arise, we can also respond with timely improvements. In June, data from 1922 SMS records was discovered by a judge assessing police search warrant applications. Concerned with the legality of wiretapping 1922 SMS, the judge questioned this use publicly.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Following discussions, the Ministry of Justice &lt;a href=&quot;https://issuu.com/pdis.tw/docs/a11000000f_11004521780a0c_?e=30178544/87054578&quot;&gt;concluded&lt;/a&gt; that the 1922 SMS does not constitute a private communication and should not be accessed as per the Communication Security and Surveillance Act. Mobile network operators and judicial authorities are now preparing measures to rule out 1922 SMS from law enforcement surveillance.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;When developing digital policies, cybersecurity and personal data protection consistently receive a great deal of attention. In Taiwan, aside from maintaining strict control over the scope of data use, we have also opened channels for the public to make inquiries concerning their own data. In this way, data is collected with citizens in mind, with citizens empowerment at its heart. This really is the core philosophy of our digital development: Data can only be appropriately used if it’s appropriately sourced.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Through collecting data via simple and secure methods, whilst using data with strict adherence to the principles of accountability, Taiwan demonstrates the meaning of efficient and popular digital innovations, as well as achieves a new milestone in digital epidemic control.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>Audrey Tang, Sheau-Tyng Peng</name></author><category term="blog" /><category term="Social Innovation" /><category term="Open Government" /><summary type="html">Data can only be appropriately used if it’s appropriately sourced.</summary><media:thumbnail xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" url="https://pdis.nat.gov.tw/en/assets/imgs/pinky-swear-329329_1280.jpg" /><media:content medium="image" url="https://pdis.nat.gov.tw/en/assets/imgs/pinky-swear-329329_1280.jpg" xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" /></entry><entry><title type="html">Smart Taiwan: Innovation, Inclusion, Sustainability</title><link href="https://pdis.nat.gov.tw/en/blog/%E6%99%BA%E6%85%A7%E5%9C%8B%E5%AE%B6-%E5%89%B5%E6%96%B0-%E5%8C%85%E5%AE%B9-%E6%B0%B8%E7%BA%8C/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Smart Taiwan: Innovation, Inclusion, Sustainability" /><published>2021-08-21T00:00:00+00:00</published><updated>2021-08-21T00:00:00+00:00</updated><id>https://pdis.nat.gov.tw/en/blog/%E6%99%BA%E6%85%A7%E5%9C%8B%E5%AE%B6-%E5%89%B5%E6%96%B0-%E5%8C%85%E5%AE%B9-%E6%B0%B8%E7%BA%8C</id><content type="html" xml:base="https://pdis.nat.gov.tw/en/blog/%E6%99%BA%E6%85%A7%E5%9C%8B%E5%AE%B6-%E5%89%B5%E6%96%B0-%E5%8C%85%E5%AE%B9-%E6%B0%B8%E7%BA%8C/">&lt;p&gt;As some of you know, I was supposed to attend the Tokyo Olympics, but unfortunately, I couldn’t make it because of the pandemic; the silver lining, though, is that I have made some friends who are interested in sports, have gained a lot of knowledge about the games, and feel like I have come to a real understanding the Olympic motto: “Faster! Higher! Stronger!”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Or, I should say, “Faster! Higher! Stronger! Together!”, after the International Olympic Committee’s (IOC) decision to include an expression of unity.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The same motto applies to the field of digital development. In the past, to strive for “faster, higher, and stronger” tech, many countries did their utmost to offer the most advanced facilities and services, to develop the most cutting-edge technologies, and to nurture high-tech “unicorns.” But more and more countries are finding that digital governance policies and promotion strategies are, like the Olympic spirit, not just about nurturing medalists, but also about bringing people together.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;President Tsai announced the platform of “Digital Nation, Smart Island” during her election campaign, and the Executive Yuan in 2017 launched the Digital Nation and Innovative Economic Development Program (DIGI⁺). After her successful re-election, it was upgraded to “Smart Taiwan 2030” this year, with the vision of a smart nation for innovation, inclusion, and sustainability by 2030.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The vision of Smart Taiwan 2030 reveals a new direction for digital governance policy. Any innovation in a modern world must be pluralistic and inclusive, with sustainable development as its goal. This means that it is no longer the case that the government is formulating policies from the top down — dictating new development paths for industries and directing people to new public services — but rather is receptive to building ecosystems of people-public-private partnerships to address problems, guided by the needs of the people.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Some people may wonder how to cater to the needs of members of the public in our diverse and rapidly evolving society and whether problems may arise as some issues are prioritized over others, but if we look back at the history of digital development, we can see that the internet was not created by an international organization or country setting standards and then building a system for people to use, but by people of all stripes, scattered around the world, working together to establish a network that connects people to each other. On this shared system, they engaged in an iterative problem-solving process of inventing protocols according to their own needs, before gradually forming the internet as we now know it, which is now indispensable for social, economic, and political activity in every corner of the world, and in a constant state of evolution as the needs of its users change.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Indeed, in a pluralistic society, people’s needs are ever shifting, and regardless of whether governments are willing to address them, there will always be people willing to tackle new problems with digital innovation. A smart national digital governance policy should not be designed to dominate or prohibit these attempts, but to find ways to align with them, which I believe is the first aspect of digital governance: alignment.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;When the COVID-19 outbreak struck last year, masks, the most essential personal protective equipment, were in short supply and the central government had to adopt a “real name registration system” for ordering face masks. Everyone wanted to know where to buy them, though, and “mask map” applications quickly appeared; the government didn’t discourage such efforts, but instead released the addresses of pharmacies selling masks and the number of masks they had in stock through open data, keeping the apps up to date.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In less than a week, more than a hundred map applications for mask availability were developed by people from all walks of life, with a wide range of configurations for use on the messaging app LINE and with voice assistance options for the blind. In other words, an alliance was forged between government, civic technologists, and the private sector, which allowed us to meet the diverse needs of the largest possible swathe of the population in the shortest possible time, and at the lowest possible cost.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;When Taiwan was hit by a wave of infections in May this year, the Central Epidemic Command Center (CECC) issued a nationwide level 3 COVID-19 alert, requiring contact information to be supplied when entering and leaving public venues to facilitate accurate contact tracing and notifications should that be needed.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;However, the long queues for registration with paper-and-pencil at each shop can be both time-consuming counterproductive in terms of virus prevention measures as the wait increases exposure time in public, so people began discussing various digital solutions, while businesses introduced their own apps for registration. From these discussions and the apps developed by the private sector, the government was able to tell what was working and what was not, and was thus able to roll out the “1922 SMS” check-in system in the shortest possible time.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;“1922 SMS” was not mandated by the central government but soon became part of people’s lives. The innovative design by the g0v (gov-zero) civic tech community proved invaluable — simply scan a QR code using the built-in smartphone camera and send the text message to 1922; no apps required.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Not only is this convenient, but it also addresses many of the concerns of the public: what if I don’t have internet access? A text message will suffice. What if I don’t have a mobile phone? You can still choose to write your contact information down on paper.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;With the SMS system, how do we store the huge amount of data being transmitted on a daily basis, though? It is stored with the telecom company providing the user’s phone service and can only be accessed by contact tracers — you can &lt;a href=&quot;https://sms.1922.gov.tw/&quot;&gt;request a full audit&lt;/a&gt; of accesses to your own records — and the information is deleted after 28 days. All of these considerations are reflected in the second aspect of digital governance: accountability.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Accountability in digital innovation puts people’s minds at ease as it inspires confidence that digital products will do what they say they will in ways that do not compromise user privacy; this is why personal data protection and cyber security are becoming increasingly important in digital development.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Moreover, accountability can ensure that improvements are made on a rolling basis as new challenges arise; for example, a judge found that evidence in a criminal investigation included data from the 1922 text messaging system and questioned its legality. Following discussions, the Ministry of Justice &lt;a href=&quot;https://issuu.com/pdis.tw/docs/a11000000f_11004521780a0c_?e=30178544/87054578&quot;&gt;concluded&lt;/a&gt; that the 1922 SMS system does not constitute a private communication and should not be accessed as per the Communication Security and Surveillance Act; mobile network operators and judicial authorities are now preparing measures to rule out 1922 SMS from law enforcement surveillance.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Following this interpretation, specific measures have now been taken by telecommunications companies and the judiciary to preclude communications surveillance from accessing the SMS data.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;As part of a national strategy for digital development, accountability is both a passive way to allay concerns and provide peace of mind and an active way to make the results of people-public-private partnerships a reality. For example, our Presidential Hackathon, which is entering its fourth year, serves as an opportunity for the public and private sectors to work together to come up with innovative ways of linking data across sectors and use digital technology to resolve social problems.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The Presidential Hackathon does not offer prize money, but the systems designed by winning teams are assured government promotion, the team is invited to be part of government initiatives, and government assistance is offered to find opportunities for commercial application.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;As Taiwan’s digital minister, what digital means foremost to me is stimulation of social innovation by increasing the connections between people through technology. In other words, the emphasis is on alignment and accountability, whereby good ideas are taken seriously, and partners can be sought out to work together, establishing a virtuous cycle that leads to innovative, inclusive, and sustainable digital development.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;To put it in another way, only when people from different sectors, fields, and roles join forces can our digital development be faster, higher, and stronger— together.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>Audrey Tang</name></author><category term="blog" /><category term="Open Government" /><category term="Social Innovation" /><summary type="html">The emphasis is on alignment and accountability, whereby good ideas are taken seriously.</summary><media:thumbnail xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" url="https://pdis.nat.gov.tw/en/assets/imgs/sustainability-3300869_1280.jpg" /><media:content medium="image" url="https://pdis.nat.gov.tw/en/assets/imgs/sustainability-3300869_1280.jpg" xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" /></entry><entry><title type="html">“Taking all the sides”</title><link href="https://pdis.nat.gov.tw/en/blog/%E9%81%B8%E6%AF%8F%E4%B8%80%E9%82%8A%E7%AB%99/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="“Taking all the sides”" /><published>2021-08-19T00:00:00+00:00</published><updated>2021-08-19T00:00:00+00:00</updated><id>https://pdis.nat.gov.tw/en/blog/%E3%80%8C%E9%81%B8%E6%AF%8F%E4%B8%80%E9%82%8A%E7%AB%99%E3%80%8D</id><content type="html" xml:base="https://pdis.nat.gov.tw/en/blog/%E9%81%B8%E6%AF%8F%E4%B8%80%E9%82%8A%E7%AB%99/">&lt;p&gt;Public policy involves everyone, with different experiences and positions. In order to achieve communication from “speaking” to “dialogue”, it is necessary to understand the ideas of all parties before they can try to promote discussion. Therefore, when our office conducts open government training courses, we often practice a mini game for civil servants: “annoying each other in one second” and “close the distance in one second.”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Why do you do this? We believe that taking some time to consider their own challenges and difficulties and establishing empathy is the first step to smoothly narrowing the distance between all parties.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We will ask everyone to imagine that the next meeting to be handled requires multiple representatives to participate. And what should be said to these people in the first sentence of the call? Let’s take the case of the joint signing of the “terminating the sacred pig weight competition” as an example. Let everyone understand that there are stakeholders in this case, such as pig farmers, animal protection groups, temples hosting competitions, etc. Let everyone enter the discussion of empathy.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Prescribing a position and drawing conclusions too quickly are common ways to irritate the other person. How to anger each other in one second? When I saw the pig farmers, I told them at the beginning: “There is a proposal from netizens to ban the sacred pig weight competition.” Or when calling the animal protection group, tell them, “Does your proposal obliterate the culture? And religious freedom?”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Take a step back and understand each other’s experience first, which can often narrow the distance between each other. “I hope you can share practical experience so that everyone can understand the difficulties of pig farmers.” If you can go further, stand on their stand and take their difficulties and challenges into consideration: “If you can’t raise pigs, your livelihood should be great. We don’t want it to be affected, so we need to hear your voice.”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Interestingly, there is often a fine line between getting closer and angering each other. For example, we invite colleagues in public affairs to think about how to invite relevant ministries to participate. Someone replied “respectfully invites members of the XX Ministry to participate” in the form of official documents, and felt that this would be fine. I don’t know that everyone likes to receive such official documents the most. Even if you send a representative to attend, you may have reservations and formal participation in experience sharing. To put it another way, if you can take the initiative to “choose each side,” explain the context of the meeting from the standpoint of all parties, and take the initiative to inquire about your wishes and ideas, colleagues in other ministries will often be more willing to invest and become partners in advancing the issue together.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Listen to each other’s difficulties, it is possible to start a dialogue. Through dialogue, it is possible for us to understand each other and come up with further solutions. In the collaborative meeting, in this way, pig farmers, animal protection groups, temple authorities, folklore experts and competent authorities can listen to each other face to face and discuss alternative ritual plans that take into account the freedom of religious sacrifice and the welfare of animals.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/assets/imgs/227d107a1cb86fee05045313785baa4fc14c901a.jpeg&quot; alt=&quot;annoying each other in one second/close the distance in one second&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>Audrey Tang, Haoting Chang</name></author><category term="blog" /><category term="Open Government" /><summary type="html">What's interesting is that there is often a fine line between getting closer and angering each other.</summary><media:thumbnail xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" url="https://pdis.nat.gov.tw/en/assets/imgs/artistic-2063_1920.jpg" /><media:content medium="image" url="https://pdis.nat.gov.tw/en/assets/imgs/artistic-2063_1920.jpg" xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" /></entry></feed>